#### Contact

emily114@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/emily-stults-rn-bsn-ccrn-2b5b79103 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
ACLS
BLS
Critical Care

# Emily Stults RN, BSN, CCRN

Critical Care Resource Pool RN at John Peter Smith Hospital Dallas/Fort Worth Area

### Summary

Registered Nurse with over 7 years of experience in the Intensive Care Unit at John Peter Smith Hospital, Fort Worth's Level 1 Trauma Center. Our 36 bed ICU encompasses both surgical and medical patients, as well as cardiac patients.

I am a certified heart nurse. I provide nursing care to patients post-CABG, post-valve replacement, post-cardiac stent, and to patients on IABP.

I am CRRT certified.

I am certified to place arterial lines and cortrak devices.

BLS, ACLS, TNCC, PALS and CCRN certified.

10 months of pediatric CICU experience at Cook Children's Medical Center in Fort Worth, Texas.

I served as an EPIC super user during Cook Children's transition from Meditech to Epic.

Experience in caring for patients with congenital heart defects with ages ranging from newborn to adulthood.

#### Experience

JPS Health Network 8 years 4 months Critical Care Resource Pool RN July 2019 - Present (1 year) Fort Worth, Texas, United States

ICU Registered Nurse February 2013 - July 2019 (6 years 6 months)

Page 1 of 2

Patient Care Technician March 2012 - February 2013 (1 year)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Nurse Extern

June 2012 - August 2012 (3 months)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Participated in a six week nurse externship.

Cook Children's Health Care System Pediatric Cardiac ICU Registered Nurse June 2017 - April 2018 (11 months)

## Education

The University of Texas at Arlington
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2012)

Tarrant County College
Associate of Arts (A.A.), Liberal Arts and Sciences/Liberal
Studies · (2008 - 2010)